Do you remember the formation of the third chamber?
第三の部屋の設置を覚えていますか？
That is, it's the moment when there's a differential growth rate
つまり、それは成長速度に差がある時期です。
between the outer part of the embryo, which receives a lot of
胚の外側部分と、多くの栄養レベルを受け取る部分の間で、
trophic levels,
栄養レベル、
and the center which slows down its speed compared to the outside.
そして、外側と比較して速度が遅くなる中心。
And that creates a movement, like a tearing.
そしてそれは、引き裂かれるような動きを生み出します。
That is, it grows.
つまり、それは成長します。
and it forms a layer of cells that will appear on the edge.
そして、それは端に現れる細胞の層を作ります。
That was this first drawing, it starts here.
それは最初の絵でした、それはここから始まります。
The word "tearing" is an image.
「引き裂かれる」という言葉はイメージです。
These are growths, we shouldn't say it's tearing.
これらは成長であり、引き裂かれると言うべきではありません。
But the image is that.
しかし、イメージはそれです。
Look, compared to this center here,
見てください、ここのこの中心と比較して、
if I take this center again now, not the black one,
もし私が今この中心を再び取り上げると、黒い部分ではなく、
and I put that right there, we see that this is where it happens.
そしてそれをここに置くと、それがここで起こっていることがわかります。
And it's in this movement,
そして、この動きの中で、
of development, that this pedicle will suddenly appear here.
発達の中で、この茎が突然現れます。
Before, it was like that everywhere, if you will.
以前は、それがどこにでもあったとすれば、
And now, through this movement, it orients itself towards a point,
そして今、この動きによって、それは一点に向かって、
towards a center.
中心に向かって。
This image, this image, and then this image.
この画像、この画像、そしてこの画像。
And I'll add this one.
そしてこれを追加します。
Here's the ground.
これが地面です。
It's the differential growth rate between the peripheral part of my embryo
それは私の胚の周辺部分と、
compared to the slowed speed of the ground.
地面の遅い速度との間の成長速度の差です。
center of the embryo, which happens during the moment when the cell cluster begins
胚の中心は、細胞の幹が変化し始める瞬間に形成されます。
to change
変化する
into the vitelline cavity and the external coelom.
卵黄嚢と外体腔に。
And it's the external coelom, finally, that provides this space of convergence
そして、最終的にこの収束空間を与えるのは外体腔です。
of force
力
in the power of what we call the embryonic pedicle, which is symbolically
胚柄と呼ばれるものの力の中で、それは象徴的に
like an attachment to the arrival of the arrival of the arrival of the arrival of the arrival
到着、到着、到着、到着、到着への取り付けのように
Your mother was supported by the universe
あなたの母親は宇宙に支えられていました
and you still have your cord on your thing.
そしてあなたはまだあなたのものにあなたのコードを持っています。
But it's not yet the umbilical cord.
しかし、それはまだへその緒ではありません。
Where is the umbilical cord?
へその緒はどこですか？
Where is the embryonic pedicle? It's here.
胚柄はどこですか？ここにあります。
And at some point, due to the excessive growth of my amniotic cavity,
そしてある時点で、私の羊膜腔の過剰な成長によって、
onto the embryonic pedicle and
胚柄の上に、そして
the meeting between the embryonic pedicle and the vitelline
胚柄と卵黄嚢の出会いが
vesicle will form the umbilical cord.
臍帯を形成します。